const SensesQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What sense do we use to taste food?",
        options: ["Smell","Taste",  "Touch"],
        correct_option: "Taste"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the sense of smell called?",
        options: [ "Audition","Olfaction", "Gustation"],
        correct_option: "Olfaction"
    },
    {
        question: "Which sense helps us detect objects by touch?",
        options: [ "Taste","Touch", "Sight"],
        correct_option: "Touch"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the sense of sight called?",
        options: ["Vision", "Audition", "Olfaction"],
        correct_option: "Vision"
    },
    {
        question: "Which sense helps us perceive sound?",
        options: ["Hearing", "Taste", "Smell"],
        correct_option: "Hearing"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the sense of taste called?",
        options: ["Gustation", "Olfaction", "Audition"],
        correct_option: "Gustation"
    },
    {
        question: "Which sense helps us maintain balance and orientation?",
        options: [ "Taste","Equilibrium", "Touch"],
        correct_option: "Equilibrium"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the sense of touch also known as?",
        options: ["Tactile sense", "Gustation", "Equilibrium"],
        correct_option: "Tactile sense"
    },
    {
        question: "Which sense helps us perceive temperature?",
        options: ["Thermoreception", "Olfaction", "Audition"],
        correct_option: "Thermoreception"
    },
    {
        question: "What sense helps us detect changes in the environment?",
        options: ["Senses", "Adaptation", "Perception"],
        correct_option: "Senses"
    }
];

export default SensesQuestions;
